It's not where you're from. It's where you're at.
Step Up 2: The Streets is a music, drama, romance film directed by Jon M. Chu.
When rebellious street dancer Andie West lands at the elite Maryland School of the Arts, she
finds herself fighting to fit in while also trying to hold onto her old life.
When she joins forces with the school's hottest dancer, Chase Collins, to form a crew of
fellow outcasts to compete in Baltimore s underground dance battle The Streets.
Andie West, played by Briana Evigan.
Chase Collins, played by Robert Hoffman.
Blake Collins, played by Will Kemp.
Sophie Donovan, played by Cassie Ventura.
Robert Alexander III / 'Moose', played by Adam Sevani.
Tuck, played by Black Thomas.
Step Up 2: The Streets is a 2008 American dance film directed by Jon M.
Chu in his feature directorial debut and written by
Toni Ann Johnson and Karen Barna.
The sequel to Step Up (2006) and the second installment in the Step Up film series, it
stars Briana Evigan, Robert Hoffman, Will Kemp, and Cassie Ventura.
Once again set at the fictional Maryland School of the Arts, the story revolves around rebellious teenage street dancer Andie West
(Evigan), who lands at the elite school and finds herself fighting to fit in while also trying to hold onto her old life.
She eventually joins forces with the school's hottest dancer Chase Collins (Hoffman) to form a crew of classmate outcasts to compete in
Baltimore's underground dance battle The Streets, finding a way to live her dream while building a bridge between her two separate worlds.
Released in the United States on February 14, 2008, by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures, the film received mixed-to-negative reviews from critics, although the reviews
were better than those for its predecessor, but became a box office success, grossing $150.8 million worldwide against a production budget of $17.5 million.
A sequel, Step Up 3D, was released in August 2010.
The film explores themes of underdog, hip-hop,
street gang, scholarship, competition.
The tone is emotional.